Siege Command Simulator is created by
Jim Tze Lau using Unity and VoltanicXR.
In this game, you command troops
to siege down an enemy city.
You'll command your troops by drawing
a line to tell them where to go.
In the CAVE environment,
this is as easy as
pointing and dragging.
Troops automatically fight with enemy
troops when they are within range,
and retreat automatically
when they are
defeated.
If they retreat successfully,
they will regroup at camp.
If they are cut off during retreat,
they are eliminated permanently.
Demo mode is recommended for beginners
because in the full mode units
move faster and there are more
enemy troops.
Every once in a while, the
enemy will shut arrows at you.
You must dodge these arrows physically
in the CAVE by moving around.
If you only want to dodge the arrows,
you can try out the timed challenge,
where you have three
hit points and need to
survive for thirty seconds.
Or endless survival, where you only
have one hit point and need to
survive for as long as you can.
There is also a multiplayer mode,
where one player plays in the DASE
CAVE as the attacker trying to
protect the cannons, and another
player plays in the LED CAVE as
the defender trying to destroy the
cannons.